{
  "math1": [
    {
      "question": "23 + 14",
      "false1": "25",
      "false2": "32",
      "false3": "41",
      "correct": "37"
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 5",
      "false1": "20",
      "false2": "17",
      "false3": "16",
      "correct": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "18 - 6",
      "false1": "11",
      "false2": "13",
      "false3": "24",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 13",
      "false1": "61",
      "false2": "67",
      "false3": "83",
      "correct": "71"
    },
         {
           "question": "14 + 15",
           "false1": "20",
           "false2": "19",
           "false3": "26",
           "correct": "29"
         },
         {
           "question": "28 - 6",
           "false1": "12",
           "false2": "18",
           "false3": "24",
           "correct": "22"
         },
         {
           "question": "18 + 13",
           "false1": "21",
           "false2": "35",
           "false3": "34",
           "correct": "31"
         },
        {
          "question": "14 + 25",
          "false1": "28",
          "false2": "37",
          "false3": "26",
          "correct": "29"
        },
        {
          "question": "18 - 16",
          "false1": "3",
          "false2": "6",
          "false3": "4",
          "correct": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "3 x 3",
          "false1": "12",
          "false2": "10",
          "false3": "8",
          "correct": "9"
        }
  ],
  "math2": [
      {
        "question": "23 + 14 + 2",
        "false1": "25",
        "false2": "32",
        "false3": "41",
        "correct": "29"
      },
           {
             "question": "14 + 15 -3",
             "false1": "20",
             "false2": "19",
             "false3": "26",
             "correct": "26"
           },
           {
             "question": "28 - 6 + 6",
             "false1": "12",
             "false2": "18",
             "false3": "24",
             "correct": "28"
           },
           {
             "question": "8 x 5 ",
             "false1": "35",
             "false2": "50",
             "false3": "45",
             "correct": "40"
           },
          {
            "question": "140 + 25",
            "false1": "160",
            "false2": "155",
            "false3": "185",
            "correct": "165"
          },
          {
            "question": "18 - 16 + 7",
            "false1": "8",
            "false2": "6",
            "false3": "2",
            "correct": "9"
          },
          {
            "question": "3 x 9",
            "false1": "25",
            "false2": "39",
            "false3": "37",
            "correct": "27"
          },
                {
                  "question": "154 - 25 + 5",
                  "false1": "160",
                  "false2": "155",
                  "false3": "185",
                  "correct": "165"
                },
                {
                  "question": "18 - 6 + 7",
                  "false1": "18",
                  "false2": "16",
                  "false3": "21",
                  "correct": "19"
                },
                {
                  "question": "(3 x 9) + 5",
                  "false1": "35",
                  "false2": "30",
                  "false3": "37",
                  "correct": "32"
                }
  ],
  "math3": [
      {
        "question": "23 + 14",
        "false1": "25",
        "false2": "32",
        "false3": "41",
        "correct": "37"
      },
      {
        "question": "14 + 5",
        "false1": "20",
        "false2": "17",
        "false3": "16",
        "correct": "19"
      },
      {
        "question": "18 - 6",
        "false1": "11",
        "false2": "13",
        "false3": "24",
        "correct": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "58 + 13",
        "false1": "61",
        "false2": "67",
        "false3": "83",
        "correct": "71"
      },
           {
             "question": "14 + 15",
             "false1": "20",
             "false2": "19",
             "false3": "26",
             "correct": "29"
           },
           {
             "question": "28 - 6",
             "false1": "12",
             "false2": "18",
             "false3": "24",
             "correct": "22"
           },
           {
             "question": "18 + 13",
             "false1": "21",
             "false2": "35",
             "false3": "34",
             "correct": "31"
           },
          {
            "question": "14 + 25",
            "false1": "28",
            "false2": "37",
            "false3": "26",
            "correct": "29"
          },
          {
            "question": "18 - 16",
            "false1": "3",
            "false2": "6",
            "false3": "4",
            "correct": "2"
          },
          {
            "question": "3 x 3",
            "false1": "12",
            "false2": "10",
            "false3": "8",
            "correct": "9"
          }
    ],
    "geo1": [
          {
            "question": "Vilken är Sveriges huvudstad",
            "false1": "Malmö",
            "false2": "Göteborg",
            "false3": "Svedala",
            "correct": "Stockholm"
          }
    ],
    "geo2": [
              {
                "question": "I vilket land ligger Paris",
                "false1": "Spanien",
                "false2": "Österrike",
                "false3": "Norge",
                "correct": "Frankrike"
              }
    ],
    "geo3": [
              {
                "question": "Vilket av nordens länder är störst, sett till yta",
                "false1": "Sverige",
                "false2": "Norge",
                "false3": "Finland",
                "correct": "Danmark"
              }
    ]
}